Guide to the International Center for Transitional Justice (ICTJ) records, 1918-2020, bulk 1970-2020 RL.01304
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Geographic Files, 1918-2016; 1969-2016
  - Asia, 1918-2016
    - Iraq, 1918; 1951; 1969; 1971; 1994-2008 (Box 14-16)
      Baghdad Penal Code, Criminal Procedure: A Worldwide Study, Trials of War Criminals before the Nuerenberg Tribunals, Penal Code with amendments, Law on Criminal Proceedings with amendments, Iraqi judiciary and justice system, UNAMI contracts, essays from War Crimes Law, reparations articles, Iraqi National Congress correspondence with ICTJ, US Institute of Peace special reports, ICTJ analysis of Iraq, blueprint report on establishing rule of law, news articles, Iraq and ICTJ meetings, establishment of the Iraqi High Tribunal, UNAMI workshop on transitional justice, UN Security Council Resolutions, focus group interviews about human rights (8 folders), subject articles, Transitional Justice Strategies in Iraq ICTJ Roundtable, Amman reparations conference, Iraq IDPs and refugee UN workshop, draft analysis report by ICTJ, Human Rights Center Berkeley, and Payson Center for International Development Tulane "Iraq: Human Rights Violations, Transitional Justice, and Social Reconstruction Priorities", ICTJ Roundtable with Higher Council for Reparations, ICTJ Roundtable on Future Directions in Iraq, De Ba'athification case study drafts, US Agency for International Development report on mass graves, UN report on cases of the missing and disappeared, reports on genocide in Iraq, World Bank report, Iraqi Constitution, The Iraq Study Group report, meeting to discuss sectarian violence, UN Security Council reports, Case Western Law documents, reparations articles, Iraq finances and budget, Iraq Criminal Procedure Code, transitional justice seminar, UNAMI survey, UN and ICTJ workshop meeting notes, Kirkuk media monitoring, UMANI contract modification, UNAMI reparations workshop, De Ba'athification laws. Includes materials in Arabic.
    - Iraq: Iraqi High Tribunal, 2003-2006 (Box 17)
      Establishment of the Iraqi High Tribunal, IHT statement on victims rights, IHT statute and statute comments, IHT statement on killings and security, Human Rights Watch reports, Amnesty International reports, revised statute of the IHT, IHT training by ICTJ, IHT media coverage, IHT articles, IHT briefing papers and reviews, IHT rules, procedures, and evidence procedures, IHT-ICTJ meeting, Law of the IHT, correspondence and notes about reparations, Groatian moment, IHT Defense Office submission concerning Saddam Hussein.
    - Iraq: Anfal Trial, 2006-2008 (Box 17-18)
      Anfal Trial updates, Anfal chamber highlights, Anfal charging instruments, closing statements, defense submissions, appeal judgement, key documents, ICTJ report drafts, Anfal evidence, Anfal trial observer mission report, Anfal verdict (4 folders).
    - Iraq: Anfal Trial Audiovisual Materials and Electronic Records
      Anfal trial transcripts and trial video recordings.
      - Afal Trial Transcripts, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0196)
      - Anfal, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0195)
      - Anfal Session 1-4, 2006-08-21/2006-09-11; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0197.1-20)
        Case A1
      - Anfal Session 13-16, 2006-10-09/2006-10-17; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0200.1-22)
        Case A4
      - Anfal Session 17-20, 2006-10-18/2006-10-31; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0201.1-18)
        Case A5
      - Anfal Session 21-24, 2006-11-07/2006-11-28; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0202.1-22)
        Case A6
      - Anfal Session 25-30, 2006-11-29/2006-12-18; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0203.1-21)
        Case A7
      - Anfal Session 31-34, 2006-12-19/2007-01-08; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0204.1-21)
        Case A8
      - Anfal Session 35-40, 2007-01-11/2007-02-07; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0205.1-21)
        Case A9
      - Anfal Session 41-43, 2007-02-08/2007-02-13; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0206.1-19)
        Case A10
      - Anfal Session 44-50, 2007-02-14/2007-03-18; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0207.1-20)
        Case A11
      - Anfal Session 5-8, 2006-09-12/2006-09-18; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0198.1-19)
        Case A2
      - Anfal Session 51-57, 2007 March - 2007 May; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0208.1-21)
        Case A12
      - Anfal Session 58-59, 2007-05-09/2007-05-10; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0209.1-4)
        Case A13
      - Anfal Session 9-12, 2006-09-19/2006-09-26; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0199.1-21)
        Case A3
    - Iraq: Dujail Trial, 2005-2007 (Box 18-20)
      Dujail session notes, Dujail Trial key documents, Dujail judgement, media pool report, ICTJ and Human Rights Watch translation of Dujail Trial Chamber judgement, Dujail trial summaries, observations, and comments, media pool reports, BBC reports, news articles, external reports, Dujail appeal judgement, commentary and news reports, ICTJ briefing papers, verdicts and sentencing in Dujail, trial transcript, Human Rights Watch analysis, ICTJ judgement analysis, "Dujail: Trial and Error?" briefing paper, ICTJ trial summaries, Dujail media monitoring project, Dujail Trial Supplementary Docs vol. 1-3, Dujail Trial Original Green Dossier Index, Dujail Trial Original Green Dossier. Includes materials in Arabic.
    - Iraq: Dujail Trial Audiovisual Materials and Electronic Records
      Dujail trial transcripts, video recordings, and Saddam Hussein trial video recordings.
      - Dujail Trial Session 1-6, 2005-10-19/2005-12-21; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0211.1-20)
        Case D1
      - Dujail Trial Session 14-19, 2006-03-01/2006-04-06; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0213.1-20)
        Case D3
      - Dujail Trial Session 20-28, 2006-04-12/2006-05-24; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0214.1-20)
        Case D4
      - Dujail Trial Session 29-35, 2006-05-29/2006-06-19; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0215.1-20)
        Case D5
      - Dujail Trial Session 36-40, 2006-07-10/2006-07-27; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0216.1-22)
        Case D6
      - Dujail Trial Session 7-13, 2005-12-22/2006-02-28; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0212.1-19)
        Case D2
      - Dujail Trial Transcripts, CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0210)
        missing 3 sessions
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-01; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0050)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-01; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0051)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-02; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0052)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-02; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0053)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-13; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0054)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-13; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0055)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-14; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0056)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-14; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0057)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-02-28; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0058)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-04-05; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0059)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-04-05; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0060)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-04-05; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0061)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0062)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial, 2006-04-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0063)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 10:00am-11:00am, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0043)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 10:00am-11:00am, 2005-12-07; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0049)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 11:00am-12:00pm, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0044)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 12:00pm-1:00pm, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0045)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 3:00am-4:00am, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0038)
        Trial of Saddam Hussein at Dujail
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 4:00am-5:00am, 2005-11-28; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0035)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 4:00am-5:00am, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0039)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 5:00am-6:00am, 2005-11-28; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0036)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 5:00am-6:00am, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0040)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 6:00am-7:00am, 2005-12-05; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0037)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial Clips, 2005-10-19/2005-12-07; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0017)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 7:00am-8:00am, 2005-10-19; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0033)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 7:00am-8:00am, 2005-12-07; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0046)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 8:00am-9:00am, 2005-10-19; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0034)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 8:00am-9:00am, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0041)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 8:00am-9:00am, 2005-12-07; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0047)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 9:00am-10:00am, 2005-12-06; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0042)
      - Saddam Hussein Trial 9:00am-10:00am, 2005-12-07; VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0048)
      - Saddam Trial I, 2005; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0190)
      - Saddam Trial II, 2005; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0191)
    - Iraq Audiovisual Materials
      Materials related to Iraqi citizens voices, including the Iraq Memory Program.
      - IPA/ICTJ Policy Forum "Iraqi Voices: Attitudes Toward Transitional Justice and Social Reconstruction", 2004-05-19; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0220)
        photographs of the event
      - Iraq Memory Program, 2005; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0015)
        series of 5 DVDs in Arabic
      - Iraq Memory Program, 2005; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0016)
      - Iraq Memory Program, 2005; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0017)
      - Iraq Memory Program, 2005; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0018)
      - Iraq Memory Program, 2005; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0019)
      - Testimonies: Iraqi Witnesses to the Saddam era, 2005; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0034)
        The Iraq Memory Foundation
    - Israel/Palestine, 2000-2007; 6 folders (Box 21)
      ICTJ proposal for a reconciliation initiative between Israelis and Palestinians, meeting with human rights activists, transitional justice seminar, articles about Israeli-Palestinian peace agreements, "Preliminary Submission of the Palestine Liberation Organization to the International Commission of Inquiry", report of the Sharm el-Sheikh fact-finding committee, UN Security Council meetings, reparations proposals, Israel's' compensation law, UN General Assembly reports, Human Rights Watch report "Palestinians' Right to Return."
    - Japan, 2004-2008; 4 folders (Box 21)
      Article about sex slavery in Japan, report on the legal approach to the "Comfort Women Issue," UN University.
    - Jordan, 2002-2008; 1 folders (Box 21)
      correspondence concerning the UN mission in Iraq.
    - Jordan Audiovisual Materials
      - His Royal Highness Prince El Hassan bin Talal, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0180)
    - Kashmir, 2005-2007; 2 folders (Box 21)
      Articles about disappearances and missing persons.
    - Lebanon, 1991; 2004-2008; 16 folders (Box 21)
      Lebanon Special Tribunal project budgets, Special Tribunal media workshop notes, UN Security Council resolutions and adoptions, analysis of statutory provisions by the Special Tribunal, UN Security Council Investigation Commission, Lebanon Amnesty laws, UN correspondence to ICTJ, UN-Lebanon agreement to set up a special tribunal, comparison of the Lebanon Special Tribunal to the Iraqi Special Tribunal, ICTJ trip report, article about truth seeking in Lebanon, Lebanon Summer Intensive, ICTJ and UNAM workshop. Includes materials in Arabic.
    - Malaysia Audiovisual Materials
      - Jalan Panjang Menggapai Keadilan, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0158)
        in Malay
    - Nepal, 2006-2014; 7 folders (Box 21)
      News articles, analysis of the Nepalese election, Nepali Times issue, ICTJ reports about violence against women, Nepalese government commission on enforced disappeared persons, decision from the government to petitioners whose families were victims of human rights abuses.
    - Pakistan, 2001; 1 folders (Box 21)
      Directory of Individuals and Institutions in South Asian Strategic Studies.
    - Philippines, 2003-2004; 3 folders (Box 21)
      House Bill 1319, NGO report on the Philippine government's implementation of the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights.
    - Philippines Audiovisual Materials
      Documentary on martial law in the Philippines.
      - Batas Militar: A Documentary on Martial Law in the Philippines, 1998; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0189)
    - Russia, 2000-2001; 4 folders (Box 21)
      Report of conflict and human rights violations, subject articles, Intelligence Service Project reports, Constitution of the Russian Federation.
    - Solomon Islands, 2009; 1 folders (Box 21)
      New office checklist, ICTJ report on the reasons to establish a TRC, application for registration under the Charitable Trusts Act.
    - Sri Lanka, 2001-2016; 16 folders (Box 21-22)
      ICTJ Sri Lanka project report, newsletter of the National Peace Council of Sri Lanka, documents on the Sri Lankan peace process, Sri Lankan intelligence oversight mechanisms, news articles, ICTJ trip reports, ICTJ project proposals, ICES Colombo annual report, Amnesty International article about lessons learned, report of the UN General Secretary's Panel of Experts on Accountability in Sri Lanka, ICTJ mission report, People's Tribunal on Sri Lanka.
    - Sri Lanka Audiovisual Materials
      - Puy Kea 2 (Young Outlook), VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0074)
      - Saroja (Sri Lanka), VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0076)
    - Syria, 2011-2013; 3 folders (Box 22)
      Human Rights Data Analysis group report on killings in Syria, UN fact finding commission on Syria report on Human Council resolutions, Syrian Center for Political and Strategic Studies roadmap for Syrian transitional justice.
    - Taiwan, 2002-2008; 2 folders (Box 22)
      South China Morning post article about memorials in Taiwan.
    - Thailand, 2000-2007; 2 folders (Box 22)
      International Crisis Group report on coup impact and Thailand's emergency decree, overview of crisis and events.
    - Turkey, 2002-2005; 2 folders (Box 22)
      Articles and reports about justice and the Turkish-Armenian genocide.
    - West Papua, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 22)
      News and articles about human rights conditions in this Indonesian province.
  - Europe, 1994-2014
    Each European country contains journal articles and other publications, including ICTJ reports, related to governance, rule of law, political stability, truth and reconciliation, reparations, and human rights violations. Large portions of the European records also deal with ICTJ partnerships with European nations.
    - Multi-regional, 1994-2002; 3 folders (Box 22)
      Atlantic Philanthropies draft report, European Union involvement, articles on multiple European countries.
    - Multi-regional Audiovisual Materials
      A discussion of the European human rights system.
      - For the Record: The European Human Rights System, 2000; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0175)
    - Armenia, 2000; 1 folders (Box 22)
      article on the Armenian problem within international law.
    - Austria, 2002-2009; 1 folders (Box 22)
      Austrian Development Agency donations and conversations with ICTJ
    - Balkans, 2001-2013; 6 folders (Box 22)
      Reparations reports, US Institute of Peace special report, TRC evaluations, ICTJ country reports, ICTJ mission reports, budget strategy for the Balkans, involvement of ICTJ in TRC, strategy reports.
    - Belarus, 2001 September; 1 folders (Box 22)
      Protection of human rights in a civil society publication.
    - Belgium, 2008-2009; 1 folders (Box 22)
      Discussions between ICTJ and the Belgium government about donations to support ICTJ in the Democratic Republic of Congo.
    - Bosnia and Herzegovina, 2000-2005; 6 folders (Box 22)
      Background report on conflict, legal implementation and reforms, war crimes project, domestic prosecutions report.
    - Bosnia and Herzegovina Audiovisual Materials
      Materials related to the massacre at Srebenica and the court of Bosnia and Herzegovina's implementation project plan.
      - Massacre in Srebrenica, 1997-07-08; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0173)
      - Project Implementation Plan Progress Report (court of Bosnia and Herzegovina), 2004 October; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0185)
      - Project Implementation Plan Progress Report (court of Bosnia and Herzegovina), 2004 October; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0186)
      - Project Implementation Plan Progress Report (court of Bosnia and Herzegovina), 2004 October; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0187)
      - Srebenica, 1999; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0183)
        BBC
    - Cyprus, 2005; 1 folders (Box 22)
      Draft Annex I: creation of a reconciliation commission.
    - Czech Republic, 1994-2009; 4 folders (Box 23)
      EU seminar, articles about reparations, American Bar Association concept paper on issues for criminal procedure, intelligence services reports.
    - Denmark, 2003-2008; 1 folders (Box 23)
      Danish Institute for Human Rights contributions to ICTJ.
    - Finland, 2002-2009; 2 folders (Box 23)
      Ministry for Foreign Affairs of Finland contributions to ICTJ, development of global truth commissions.
    - France, 2004-2007; 1 folders (Box 23)
      Development coordination in France.
    - Germany, 1951; 1982-2008; 10 folders (Box 23)
      Contributions to ICTJ, reparations reports, transitional justice in East Germany, news articles, Germany-Israel Agreement, law for victims of Nazi persecution, Bundestag Enquete-Kommission, German Federal Government Action Plan and prosecution of Nazi war criminals, Germany after Nazism articles, German intelligence reports.
    - Hungary, 1992-2002; 2 folders (Box 23)
      Development of a fellowship program, reparations reports.
    - Ireland/Northern Ireland, 1995-2008; 13 folders (Box 23, 143)
      Healing Through Remembering project, loyalist parliamentary murders, Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission reports, prosecutions, victims' rights, Sentencing Act, ICTJ trip reports, subject articles, reconciliation and healing projects, Irish aid to Timor and Liberia, Belfast conference, Atlantic Philanthropists reports. Box 143 contains photos from a trip to Northern Ireland.
    - Italy, 2007-2009; 3 folders (Box 23)
      Workshop on transitional justice and how Italy can help its closest neighbors, Italian vocabulary, contributions to ICTJ.
    - Kosovo, 1999-2005; 6 folders (Box 23)
      ICTJ mission in Kosovo, legal system analysis, UN and UNICEF programs in Kosovo, UN Security Council reports and resolution.
    - Latvia, 1999; 1 folders (Box 23)
      Article: Latvian Prison Administration transfer to the Department of the Interior.
    - Liechtenstein, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 23)
      Contributions to ICTJ, invitation to ICTJ to attend a conference, permanent mission of Liechtenstein to the UN.
    - Luxembourg, 2005-2009; 1 folders (Box 23)
      Contributions to ICTJ.
    - Macedonia, 2008; 1 folders (Box 24)
      Information about the new Minister for Foreign Investment.
    - The Netherlands, 2004-2009; 3 folders (Box 24)
      Contributions to ICTJ, the Netherlands Quarterly of Human Rights issue, invitations to conferences, ICTJ speaking opportunities in the Netherlands.
    - Norway, 2001-2009; 2 folders (Box 24)
      Contributions to ICTJ, grant programs, cooperative agreement with ICTJ.
    - Romania, 2001; 1 folders (Box 24)
      Intelligence services.
    - Serbia, 1999-2008; 4 folders (Box 24)
      Open Society Justice Initiative report on the impact of ICTY, news articles, peace strategy, ICTJ project information, articles about justice in Serbia.
    - Serbia Audiovisual Materials
      - B92 Documentary "Bitter Medicine", 2003; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0174)
      - Belgrade Coffee Shop 2, 2001; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0188)
      - Fry-Abduction Serbia, 1992; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0175)
      - The Scorpions: A Home Movie, 2007; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0039)
      - Video on Serbia War, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0176)
    - Spain, 2002-2009; 9 folders (Box 24)
      Reports on transitional justice in Spain, subject articles, conflict background information, ICTJ project proposal, correspondence about permanent work of UN in Spain, ICTJ report "Justicia Transicional en Espana."
    - Sweden, 2000-2009; 4 folders (Box 24)
      Intelligence oversight report, contributions to ICTJ, Swedish National Defence College conference.
    - Switzerland, 2003-2009; 1 folders (Box 24)
      Contributions to ICTJ, attendance at conferences, correspondence about conference attendance.
    - United Kingdom, 2000-2009; 3 folders (Box 24)
      Intelligence oversight reports, DFID participation.
    - United Kingdom Audiovisual Materials
      - Firing Line 93: English Youth and Vietnam, 1968-02-27; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0075)
    - Ukraine, 2013-2014; 1 folders (Box 24)
      ICTJ country report and forecast, transitional justice in Ukraine, human rights in Ukraine, European Commission for Implementation, UN report on human rights in Ukraine.
    - Yugoslavia/Former Yugoslavia, 1998-2002; 6 folders (Box 24)
      Conflict in Yugoslavia, ICTY in Yugoslavia report, articles about Yugoslavian conflict, special reports, letters to President Kostunica and members of the TRC from ICTJ.
    - Yugoslavia Audiovisual Materials
      Milosevic Trial and judgements.
      - Exemplary Excerpts from prosecution in Milosevic Trial, DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0020)
        2 discs
      - Haradinaj Judgement, 2008-04-03; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0013)
        International Criminal Tribunal for the former Yugoslavia
      - Milosevic, 2002-11-19; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0002)
      - Milosevic, 2002-11-19; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0003)
      - Milosevic, 2002-11-19; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0004)
      - Milosevic, 2005-05-06; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0007)
      - Milosevic Pre-Defence Conference, 2004-06-17; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0005)
      - Milosevic Pre-Defence Conference, 2004-06-17; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0006)
      - Milosevic trial SENSE News Agency Archive, 2006-07-08; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0011)
      - Milosevic trial SENSE News Agency Archive, 2006-07-08; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0012)
      - Milsosevic, 2005-12-12; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0008)
      - Milsosevic, 2005-12-12; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0009)
      - Milsosevic, 2005-12-12; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0010)
      - Sense Tribunal, 2002-08-02; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0172)
      - Tadic Sentence, 1997-07-14; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0001)
  - North America/Caribbean, 1982-2009